Baylor-Carrington Family papers, Inclusive: 1715-2007, undated, Bulk: 1840-1930
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Baylor-Carrington Family papers
Inclusive: 1715-2007, undated, Bulk: 1840-1930
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
170
Carrington, Addie Baylor, 1897 - 1984
18 documents boxes and 6 oversized boxes
The Baylor-Carrington Family papers consist of correspondence, financial and legal documents, literary productions, books, photographs, artifacts, and scrapbooks pertaining to the Baylor and Carrington families. The collection spans from the American Revolution to the mid-1900s.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
The Baylor family arrived in America around 1690, when John Baylor II migrated from England. He was later joined by his father, John I, and in 1721 the family received a large land grant in Virginia. John II and his son, John III, were both members of the Virginia House of Burgesses. Two of John III’s sons served as officers in the American Revolution: George (1752-1784) was an aide-de-camp for George Washington and Walker (1762-1822) served as captain of the Third Continental Dragoons (also known as Baylor’s Dragoons).
Walker began the family’s westward migration by moving to Kentucky in 1783; his sons and grandsons were the ancestors of the Texas Baylors. Robert Emmett Bledsoe Baylor (1793-1873), son of Walker and Jane Bledsoe, moved first to Alabama and then to Texas. He fought in the War of 1812 and became a legislator, lawyer, and pioneering Baptist leader. Baylor University is named for him. Many of his male relatives followed a similar pattern of migration and political and military involvement.
John Walker VIII (1786-1835), Robert’s brother, had a number of sons who went west and participated in the Texas Revolution, the Civil War, and various wars against the American Indians. One son, George Wythe (1832-1916) graduated from Baylor University and fought Comanche Indians in 1859-1860. During the Civil War, George Wythe served as aide-de-camp to fellow Texan Albert Sidney Johnston, and later served as the colonel of the Second Arizona Cavalry. After the war, he joined the Texas Rangers, rising to the rank of major. In 1880, George Wythe served in the Texas House of Representatives. One of his grandsons, James Harper Baylor Lee-Gillette (1884-1941), was the first American matador. Another of John Walker VIII’s sons, Henry Weidner (1818-1854), went west in 1839. He served in the Texas Revolution, and was eventually elected captain of a company. Baylor County, Texas, is named in his honor.
The most prominent of John Walker VIII’s sons was John Robert (1822-1894). In the early 1840s, John Robert fought in the Texas Revolution. Afterwards, he took it upon himself to destroy the Comanche Indians. He traveled around Texas stirring up anti-Indian sentiment, edited an anti-Indian newspaper called White Man, and even raised a vigilante force of 1,000 men. He served in the Texas legislature from 1852-1854. During the Civil War, John Robert was commissioned as Confederate lieutenant colonelDLand later became a colonelDLin command of the Second Texas Mounted Rifles. He organized the Confederate Territory of Arizona and served as its military governor. After John Robert planned the massacre of a group of Apaches in 1862, Confederate President Jefferson Davis stripped him of command. By that time, higher-ranking Henry Hopkins Sibley was leading the 1862 Confederate Invasion of New Mexico, which meant John Robert would not have been in command of the Arizona territory anyway. John Robert fought as a private in the 1863 Battle of Galveston and subsequently served in the Second Confederate Congress. He was married to Emily Jane Hanna (1825-1917).
One of John Robert’s sons, Henry Weidner IV (1848-1932), was a private under his uncle George Wythe during the Civil War. Later he served as the sheriff of Uvalde County for twenty-two years and as the tax assessor for twelve. Henry Weidner IV was married to Addie DeLeon Hamer (1851-1894), after whose death he married Florence Black. His grandson, John Roy XVII (1899-1918), served as a sergeant in the United States Army during World War I until his death in France in October 1918. John Roy XVII’s sister, Addie (1897-1984), was a school teacher in Marquez, Texas. She was active in organizing the 1930 Baylor family reunion (one among a few reunions in the 1930s and 1940s). This collection owes much to Addie's efforts to collect and preserve her family history. Addie married Royle Pruitt Carrington, among whose nineteenth-century ancestors was an active Texas lawyer. As a group, the Baylor family has been interested in its history; they established a family organization and for a while published a magazine dedicated to the family history. These activities, along with many Baylors and their long history, are represented in the Baylor-Carrington Family Papers.
Scope and Content
The Baylor-Carrington Family papers cover a century and a half of Baylor and American history, from 1715 to 1978, although the bulk of the materials are from 1840 to 1930. Baylor men of prominence were involved in the American Revolution, the Texas Revolution, Indian fighting with the Texas Rangers, the Civil War, and World War I -- all of which are represented in this collection. This collection includes records produced by several generations of Baylors, most of whom lived and worked in Texas. These records are of both personal and professional natures, and include a large amount of correspondence (especially between family members). The literary productions series is the largest and includes biographical and genealogical materials about Baylor and other families. In addition to documents, this collection contains photographs, books, scrapbooks, and artifacts.
Arrangement
Most of the Baylor-Carrington Family papers were organized prior to this finding aid, although there were a number of entirely unprocessed boxes.
The collection is now organized into eight series: I. Correspondence, II. Legal Documents, III. Financial Documents, IV. Literary Productions, V. Books, VI. Photographic Materials, VII. Artifacts, and VIII. Scrapbooks. Where possible, items are arranged chronologically.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 170. Acquired 1935-02-00
Related Resources
Items in related collections
Robert Emmett Bledsoe Baylor papers, Inclusive: 1812-1981, undated, Bulk: 1837-1873
Related references
Cutrer, Thomas W. “Baylor, George Wythe.” Handbook of Texas Online. Accessed 2012 October 8.
Cutrer, Thomas W. “Baylor, Henry Weidner.” Handbook of Texas Online. Accessed 2012 October 8.
Lea, Tom. “Gillett, James Harper [Harper Baylor Lee].” Handbook of Texas Online. Accessed 2012 October 8.
Summerlin, Travis L. “Baylor, Robert Emmett Bledsoe.” Handbook of Texas Online. Accessed 2012 October 8.
Thompson, Jerry. “Baylor, John Robert.” Handbook of Texas Online. Accessed 2012 October 8.
Walraven, Bill. “Baylor, John Walker. Handbook of Texas Online. Accessed 2012 October 8.
Electronic Resources
Collection Files
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Baylor family.; Baylor, George Wythe, 1832-1916.; Baylor, George Wythe, 1858-; Baylor, Henry Weidner, 1818-1854.; Baylor, Henry Weidner, 1848-1932.; Baylor, John Robert, 1822-1894.
Subjects (Organizations)
Texas Rangers -- History.
Places
Texas -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865.; Texas -- History -- Revolution, 1835-1836.; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865.; United States -- History -- Revolution, 1775-1783.
Subjects
Genealogy.; Postcards.; World War, 1914-1918.
Genres
Brochures.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Contracts.; Correspondence.; Essays.; Legal documents.; Periodicals.; Photographs.; Research notes.; Scrapbooks.; Speeches.
- Correspondence, 1715-1969; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  This series contains personal and professional correspondence from several generations of Baylors and Carringtons. While most of the series is in good condition, Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor's letters are in poor condition. Much of Emily "Emy" Jane Hanna Baylor's correspondence is from her husband, John Robert Baylor. Of particular note is a copy of a letter from Robert E. Lee to John Robert Baylor.
  - General, 1844 January 18-1894 February 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General, 1897 January 1-1938 January 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General (1 of 2), undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General (2 of 2), undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - George Baylor and George Washington, 1775 July 12-1777 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - George Baylor and George Washington, 1777 February 15-1777 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - George Baylor and George Washington, 1778 March 4-1778 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - George Baylor and George Washington, 1778 June 6-1778 September 22 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - George Baylor and Daniel Clark, 1783 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - D. C. Carrington, 1826 August 7-1851 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - D. C. Carrington, 1852 September 25-1943 February 18 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - John G. Walker, 1849 March 20-1861 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - John G. Walker, 1861 July-1861 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Henry W. Baylor, 1846 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1852 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Walker Keith Baylor, 1858 January 7-1862 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Walker Keith Baylor, 1869 August 26-1894 March 12, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - From Robert E. Lee to John Robert Baylor, 1856 January 12 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - John Robert Baylor, 1852 December 20-1853 November 28 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - John Robert Baylor, 1854 August 1-1855 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - John Robert Baylor, 1856 January 12-1856 December 15 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - John Robert Baylor, 1858 June 4-1861 May 30 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - John Robert Baylor, 1861 August 3-1869 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - John Robert Baylor (1 of 4), 1861 July 7-1865 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - John Robert Baylor (2 of 4), 1861 July 7-1865 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - John Robert Baylor (3 of 4), 1861 July 7-1865 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - John Robert Baylor (4 of 4), 1861 July 7-1865 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - John Robert Baylor (1 of 2), undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - John Robert Baylor (2 of 2), undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - From John Robert Baylor to Frances “Fan” Baylor Belger, 1852 July 24-1855 January 13 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - From John Robert Baylor to Frances “Fan” Baylor Belger, 1855 March 11-1856 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - From John Robert Baylor to Frances “Fan” Baylor Belger, 1856 December 15-1857 April 28, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Emily “Emy” Jane Hanna Baylor, 1853 November 9-1854 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Emily “Emy” Jane Hanna Baylor, 1855 December 9-1861 September 20 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Emily “Emy” Jane Hanna Baylor, 1862 January 12-1899 December 23 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Emily “Emy” Jane Hanna Baylor, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1902 November 12-1903 February 12 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1903 April 16-1904 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1904 February 19-1904 September 21 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1904 September 27-1905 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1905 November 7-1906 March 6 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1906 June 13-1906 August 26 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1906 October 5 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1906 November 20-1907 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1907 July 18-1908 August 9 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1908 September 11-1909 April 19 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1909 October 8-1910 December 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - George Wythe Baylor, 1939 October 10-November 20 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Henry Weidner Baylor, 1897 July 19, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor, 1873 July 5-1875 January (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor, 1875 September 19-1893 July 4 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - John Roy Baylor, 1898 December 9-1899 June 20 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - John Roy Baylor, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - James Drucilla Allen, 1919 April 20, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Susan Hamer Baylor Illg, 1905 December 6, 1922 August 31, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - From Sue Hamer Baylor Illg to Addie Baylor Carrington (1 of 10), 1930-1968 July 13, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - From Sue Hamer Baylor Illg to Addie Baylor Carrington (2 of 10), 1930-1968 July 13, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - From Sue Hamer Baylor Illg to Addie Baylor Carrington (3 of 10), 1930-1968 July 13, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - From Sue Hamer Baylor Illg to Addie Baylor Carrington (4 of 10), 1930-1968 July 13, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - From Sue Hamer Baylor Illg to Addie Baylor Carrington (5 of 10), 1930-1968 July 13, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - From Sue Hamer Baylor Illg to Addie Baylor Carrington (6 of 10), 1930-1968 July 13, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - From Sue Hamer Baylor Illg to Addie Baylor Carrington (7 of 10), 1930-1968 July 13, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - From Sue Hamer Baylor Illg to Addie Baylor Carrington (8 of 10), 1930-1968 July 13, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - From Sue Hamer Baylor Illg to Addie Baylor Carrington (9 of 10), 1930-1968 July 13, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - From Sue Hamer Baylor Illg to Addie Baylor Carrington (10 of 10), 1930-1968 July 13, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1906 October 15-1908 February 10 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1908 October 11-1908 October 25 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1908 November 8-1911 April 4 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1914 May 29-1918 May 7 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1918 August 2-1921 January 21 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1928 February 25-1930 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1930 June 10-1930 December 26 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1931 January 27-1931 March 1 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1931 March 15-1931 April 12 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1931 May 15-1931 June 21 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1932 June 2-1932 October 19 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1932 November 15-1933 June 7 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1933 June 24-1937 December 22 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1938 April 4-1939 January 21 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1939 January 23-1939 February 6 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1939 February 13-1939 December 28 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1940 January 23-1941 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1941 June 24-1958 March 17 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1959 May 20 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1964 June 10-1968 January 6 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington, 1968 January 13-1969 October 26 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington (1 of 3), undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington (2 of 3), undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington (3 of 3), undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Telegrams: Addie Baylor Carrington, 1928 May 29-1932 October 12, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - From Addie Baylor Carrington to Mrs. F. A. Maxwell, 1935 November 7, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - From Stephen Decatur to Addie Baylor Carrington, 1957 December 12-1958 May 9 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - From Stephen Decatur to Addie Baylor Carrington, 1958 June 14-1959 February 4 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - From Stephen Decatur to Addie Baylor Carrington, 1959 February 12-1959 June 10 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - From Stephen Decatur to Addie Baylor Carrington, 1959 June 20-1960 June 6 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - From Stephen Decatur to Addie Baylor Carrington, 1960 July 9-1961 November 28 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Royle Pruitt Carrington, 1912 September 29-1913 October 1 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Royle Pruitt Carrington, 1913 October 10-1932 August 20, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington and Royle Pruitt Carrington, 1920 July 4-1932 June 29 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington and Royle Pruitt Carrington, 1932 July 1-1932 July 4 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington and Royle Pruitt Carrington, 1932 July 6-1938 November 10 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington and Royle Pruitt Carrington, 1943 December 16-1943 December 20 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Addie Baylor Carrington and Royle Pruitt Carrington, 1943 December 21-1965 November 19, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Baylor Family Reunions: General, 1929 June 6-1939 May 1, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 1928 Baylor Family Reunion, 1928 March 1-1928 March 14 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 1930 Baylor Family Reunion, 1928 May 30-1930 February 24 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 1930 Baylor Family Reunion, 1930 March 5-1930 May 14 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 1932 Baylor Family Reunion, 1932 June 5 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - 1939 Baylor Family Reunion, 1939 May 15-1939 June 22 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Baylor Family Relations: Lily M. Russell, 1935 January 8-1935 May 17 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Baylor Family Relations: Lily M. Russell, 1935 May 19-1935 June 22 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Susan Baylor Adams, 1969 January 1-March 26 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Legal Documents, 1770-1907; 2
  This series consists of a variety of legal documents from the Baylor and Carrington families. The majority of the series, however, is a dense run of contracts from the Carrington family--covering from the 1830s to the 1910s. Of particular note is John L. Wall's contract signed by the president of the Republic of Texas, Mirabeau B. Lamar, as well as John Robert Baylor's pass to move about the Confederate States of America signed by Secretary of State Judah P. Benjamin.
  - Last Wills and Testaments: John Baylor, 1770 February 19 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Deeds: John Baylor, undated (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: Walker Baylor and William Miller Bledsoe, 1786 June 30-1789 September (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Contracts: Walker Baylor and William Miller Bledsoe, 1799 September 13, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Contracts: John L. Wall, 1841 August 9 (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 11)
  - General: John Robert Baylor, 1865 March 8 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - General: George Wythe Baylor, 1897 October 21-1908 February 25 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - General: Baylor Family, 1880 August 9-1891 September 7 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Certificate of Election: Henry Weidner Baylor, 1900 November 14 (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1836 May 31-1841 August 6 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1841 August 25-1885 September 17 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1846 May 21-1847 January 23 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1847 September 8-1848 July 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1849 February 27-1849 November 20 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1850 December 13-1877 December 4 (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1851 February 1-1853 September 12 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1854 July 6-1856 September 15 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1858 January 6-1858 December 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1859 March 1-1859 December 12 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1860 January 20-1860 September 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1860 October 1-1861 April 12 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1862 January 10-1863 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1864 March 19-1867 March 13 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1868 February 7-1868 November 4 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1868 November 30-1870 January 3 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1870 July 24-1871 August 10 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1871 August 11-1872 March 30 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1872 July 30-1872 October 17 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1873 January 1-1873 July (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1873 July 30 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1874 January 13-1874 January 19 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1874 March 16-1875 January 27 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1876 February 5-1876 December 9 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1877 March 3-1877 July 4 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1877 November 24-1878 May 24 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1878 July 15-1879 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1879 July 2-1880 February 5 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1880 March 26-1880 July 17 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1880 October 3-1881 April 23 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1881 June 4-1881 August 22 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1882 January 28-1882 March 10 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1882 April 2-1882 September 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1882 September 9-1882 October 12 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1882 December 19-1883 January 12 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1883 June 7-1883 November 6 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1883 December 1-1884 April 9 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1884 September 4-1884 December 29 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1885 May 29-1887 March 31 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1887 October 7-1887 December 14 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1887 December 27-1888 August (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1888 October 2-1888 November 19 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1888 December 6 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1889 January 6-1889 February 5 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1889 April 25-1889 December 27 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1890 January 17-1890 October 4 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1890 November 24-1892 May 15 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1892 June 7-1892 December 30 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1895 August 15-1893 December 4 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1894 February 19-1894 August 23 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1895 January 23-1895 August 5 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1895 August 6-1895 October 5 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1895 December 13-1898 June 3 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Contracts: Carrington Family, 1878 July 8-1903 September 12 (Box 5, Folder 23)